<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Matej Varga</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Matej Varga</description>
    <generator>Hugo 0.125.2</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Link to heading All my links (Linktree) is available here Digital visit card (vcard) can be downloaded here Digital visit card (vcard) scan:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/about/</guid>
      <description>I am working as a postdoctoral scientist and teaching assistant at the ETH Zürich, Institute of Geodesy and Photogrammetry in the group of Geosensors and Engineering Geodesy led by Prof. Dr. Andreas Wieser.&#xA;I am passionate about geospatial data collection and processing using different measurement systems and applications. Instruments which I have specialised are GNSS, total station, level, terrestrial laser scanner, laser tracker, camera, radar, gravimeter, and magnetometer.&#xA;Contents Link to heading Introduction Contact Biography Professional Networks News Recent Projects Professional Interests and Activities Selected Contributions Teaching Academic And Industry Collaborations Supervising Students and Researchers Offered student topics Community Lists That I am Maintaining GitHub Metrics News Link to heading [2024/02/15]: Leading several student projects, including (i)smartphone navigation using ML and factor graph optimization, (ii) total station and laser scanning testing and calibration, and (iii) 3D modelling of Lausanne Cathedral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/cv/</guid>
      <description> Previous Next &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; / [pdf] View the PDF file here. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/publications/</guid>
      <description>Books Link to heading Varga, M. (2020): Geometrical geodesy (in Croatian). Varga, M. (2020): Physical geodesy (in Croatian, revision in progress). Project reports Link to heading Varga, M., Wieser, A. (2024): Concept for calibration, checking and testing of the geodetic equipment for the FCC. Deliverable IGP-AA-2.5. CHART project FCC-Geodesy IGP-AA-2.&#xA;Varga, M., Wieser, A. (2024): Conceptual design report for the connection of the geodetic underground monitoring system to the civil engineering one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/research/</guid>
      <description>Books Link to heading Varga, M. (2020): Geometrical geodesy (in Croatian). Varga, M. (2020): Physical geodesy (in Croatian, revision in progress). Project reports Link to heading Varga, M., Wieser, A. (2024): Concept for calibration, checking and testing of the geodetic equipment for the FCC. Deliverable IGP-AA-2.5. CHART project FCC-Geodesy IGP-AA-2.&#xA;Varga, M., Wieser, A. (2024): Conceptual design report for the connection of the geodetic underground monitoring system to the civil engineering one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Lectures, exercises, seminars Link to heading Course name Total semesters Responsibilities Engineering Geodesy 4 E, S, C Geospatial Reference Systems and Geometrical Geodesy 11 L, E, S Physical Geodesy 8 L, E Geophysical Geodesy 6 S Geomagnetism 6 E, S, C Satellite Geodesy 5 E, C Global Geodesy 5 S Navigation 2 E, C Analysis and Processing of Geodetic Measurements 2 E Industrial Metrology and Machine Vision 1 S Special algorithms for processing geodetic measurements 1 E &amp;#x26a0;&amp;#xfe0f; L: lectures, E: exercises, S: seminar, C: field campaigns Supervising students and researchers Link to heading I am accepting the supervision of responsible and motivated internal (ETHZ) and external students at the BSc, MSc, and PhD levels.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
