<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Matej Varga</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Matej Varga</description>
    <generator>Hugo 0.125.2</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:18:15 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>E-scooter positioning in urban environments</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/thesistopics/e_scooter_positioning_in_urban_environments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 10:21:19 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/thesistopics/e_scooter_positioning_in_urban_environments/</guid>
      <description>Information Link to heading Chair/professorship: Geosensors and Engineering Geodesy (GSEG)&#xA;Supervisor: Prof. Dr. Andreas Wieser&#xA;Advisor: Matej Varga&#xA;Suitable for: BSc/Mc/Master project&#xA;Number of students per group: 1-4&#xA;Maximum number of groups 1&#xA;Abstract Link to heading E-scooters in cities rely on sensors for positioning which can only provide 3-10 meters accuracy. Many applications require sub-meter accuracy in real time. Installing expensive, high-quality hardware on large number of e-scooters is costly and impractical.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance of an e-Scooter&#43;IPhone mobile mapping system</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/thesistopics/performance_of_e_scooter_iphone_14_mobile_mapping_system/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 10:21:19 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/thesistopics/performance_of_e_scooter_iphone_14_mobile_mapping_system/</guid>
      <description>Information Link to heading Chair/professorship: Geosensors and Engineering Geodesy (GSEG)&#xA;Supervisor: Prof. Dr. Andreas Wieser&#xA;Advisor: Matej Varga&#xA;Suitable for: BSc/Mc/Master project&#xA;Number of students per group: 1-3&#xA;Maximum number of groups 1&#xA;Abstract Link to heading Cities are constantly developing, demanding frequent updates of geospatial data and models. For instance, the City of Zürich maintains a detailed 3D city model (LOD2) with over 480 thematic layers (e.g., green spaces, bike paths, construction zones).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Link to heading All my links (Linktree) are available here Digital visit card (vcard) can be downloaded here Digital visit card (vcard) scan:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/about/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Link to heading Introduction Interests and Activities Research portfolio Projects Academic and industry collaborations News Introduction Link to heading I am working as a postdoctoral scientist, lecturer and teaching assistant at the ETH Zürich, Institute of Geodesy and Photogrammetry in the group of Geosensors and Engineering Geodesy led by Prof. Dr. Andreas Wieser.&#xA;I am passionate about collecting, analyzing, integration and interpretation of geospatial data from different measurement systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consultancy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/consultancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/consultancy/</guid>
      <description>s Scientific and academic consultancy&#xA;academic advertisement Website &amp;amp; Social Media LinkedIn profile academic web-pages paper dissemination Curriculum Vitae (CV) Preparation academic career planning publication strategy development support in thesis planning and proposals post-graduation planning job application and interview preparation coaching academic networking building professional networks research proposal development grant writing project planning project, papers and presentation preparation conference presentation preparation and rehearsal paper revision proofreading figures preparation references suggestion literature review assistance english language and grammar corrections geospatial data analysis and Interpretation programming in Matlab, Python and Fortran images preparation in open-source software packages (e.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/cv/</guid>
      <description> Previous Next &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; / [pdf] View the PDF file here. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/publications/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Link to heading Books Project reports Articles in international journals Articles in other journals International and national oral presentations, conference proceeding papers and posters Presentations and other contributions Mentoring and supervision Books Link to heading Varga, M. (2020): Geometrical geodesy (in Croatian). Varga, M. (2020): Physical geodesy (in Croatian, revision in progress). Project reports Link to heading Varga, M., Wieser, A. (2024): Concept for calibration, checking and testing of the geodetic equipment for the FCC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervision of students and researchers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/supervision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/supervision/</guid>
      <description>I am happy to accept supervision of responsible and motivated internal (ETHZ) and external students at the BSc, MSc, and PhD levels.&#xA;Topics are not predetermined and can be adapted to student&amp;rsquo;s preferences and ideas. If you have an idea and wish to pursue your topic within my research scope, please prepare a brief research plan.&#xA;Most of the topics can be taken as a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s, Master’s thesis, or even adapted as a Master&amp;rsquo;s project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Matej_Varga/teaching/</guid>
      <description> Lectures, exercises, seminars Link to heading Course name Total semesters Responsibilities Engineering Geodesy 4 E, S, C Geospatial Reference Systems and Geometrical Geodesy 11 L, E, S Physical Geodesy 8 L, E Geophysical Geodesy 6 S Geomagnetism 6 E, S, C Satellite Geodesy 5 E, C Global Geodesy 5 S Navigation 2 E, C Analysis and Processing of Geodetic Measurements 2 E Industrial Metrology and Machine Vision 1 S Special algorithms for processing geodetic measurements 1 E &amp;#x26a0;&amp;#xfe0f; L: lectures, E: exercises, S: seminar, C: field campaigns </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
