<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Matej Varga</title>
    <link>http://localhost:57435/Matej_Varga/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Matej Varga</description>
    <generator>Hugo 0.125.2</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 10:21:19 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:57435/Matej_Varga/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>E-scooter positioning in urban environments</title>
      <link>http://localhost:57435/Matej_Varga/thesis/e-scooter_positioning_in_urban_environments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 10:21:19 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:57435/Matej_Varga/thesis/e-scooter_positioning_in_urban_environments/</guid>
      <description>Information Link to heading Chair/professorship: Geosensors and Engineering Geodesy (GSEG) Supervisor: Prof. Dr. Andreas Wieser Advisor: Matej Varga Suitable for: BSc/Mc/Master project Number of students per group: 1-4 Maximum number of groups 1&#xA;Abstract Link to heading E-scooters in cities rely on sensors for positioning which can only provide 3-10 meters accuracy. Many applications require sub-meter accuracy in real time. Installing expensive, high-quality hardware on large number of e-scooters is costly and impractical.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:57435/Matej_Varga/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:57435/Matej_Varga/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Link to heading All my links (Linktree) are available here Digital visit card (vcard) can be downloaded here Digital visit card (vcard) scan:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:57435/Matej_Varga/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:57435/Matej_Varga/about/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Link to heading Introduction Interests and Activities Research portfolio Projects Academic and industry collaborations News Introduction Link to heading I am working as a postdoctoral scientist, lecturer and teaching assistant at the ETH Zürich, Institute of Geodesy and Photogrammetry in the group of Geosensors and Engineering Geodesy led by Prof. Dr. Andreas Wieser.&#xA;I am passionate about collecting, analyzing, integration and interpretation of geospatial data from different measurement systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>http://localhost:57435/Matej_Varga/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:57435/Matej_Varga/cv/</guid>
      <description> Previous Next &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; / [pdf] View the PDF file here. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://localhost:57435/Matej_Varga/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:57435/Matej_Varga/publications/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Link to heading Books Project reports Articles in international journals Articles in other journals International and national oral presentations, conference proceeding papers and posters Presentations and other contributions Mentoring and supervision Books Link to heading Varga, M. (2020): Geometrical geodesy (in Croatian). Varga, M. (2020): Physical geodesy (in Croatian, revision in progress). Project reports Link to heading Varga, M., Wieser, A. (2024): Concept for calibration, checking and testing of the geodetic equipment for the FCC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>http://localhost:57435/Matej_Varga/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:57435/Matej_Varga/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents Link to heading Lectures, exercises, seminars Supervising students and researchers Offered (open) topics Supervised students Lectures, exercises, seminars Link to heading Course name Total semesters Responsibilities Engineering Geodesy 4 E, S, C Geospatial Reference Systems and Geometrical Geodesy 11 L, E, S Physical Geodesy 8 L, E Geophysical Geodesy 6 S Geomagnetism 6 E, S, C Satellite Geodesy 5 E, C Global Geodesy 5 S Navigation 2 E, C Analysis and Processing of Geodetic Measurements 2 E Industrial Metrology and Machine Vision 1 S Special algorithms for processing geodetic measurements 1 E &amp;#x26a0;&amp;#xfe0f; L: lectures, E: exercises, S: seminar, C: field campaigns Supervising students and researchers Link to heading I am happy to accept supervision of responsible and motivated internal (ETHZ) and external students at the BSc, MSc, and PhD levels.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
